(Sheldon:)Take me to Leonard.
(Amy:)Just go to work,
he'll be fine.
(Sheldon:)Amy, he's my best friend,
and if you don't take me,
(Sheldon:)I'm going there anyway.
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Amy:)It's sweet that you
care about him so much.
(Sheldon:)I do.
(Sheldon:)And I wouldn't
be able to forgive myself,
(Sheldon:)if something happened to him
and I wasn't at his bedside
to say, "I told you so."
(Amy:)Hello.
(Penny:)We had a really nice swim.
(Sheldon:)Oh, stop it.
(Sheldon:)I assume this medical
center's already treated
(Sheldon:)the burns on your bottom
from the recent pants fire.
'Cause I'm a liar, liar?
(Sheldon:)That's for the fire marshal
to determine.
(Penny:)You had to tell him?
(Amy:)He wore me down.